https://sci.ngo/privacy-cookie-policy/

Privacy and Cookie Policy - Service Civil International
MENUMENUHomeAbout usWho we areAnnual ReportStrategic PlanOur HistoryOur MovementWhere we areBecome our partnerSupport and partner networksGet involvedVolunteer with usWorkcampsLong Term VolunteeringEvents and training coursesOur workInternational VolunteeringThemesClimateRefugeesGenderProjectsPeace in Practice100 years celebration!ResourcesOur publicationsVoices of VolunteersContact usDonate
Select Page
Privacy and Cookie PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how The Association of Service Civil International ivzw (SCI) uses and protects any information that you give SCI when you use this website (www.sci.ngo).SCI is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.SCI may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 25 May 2018.1. Data collected and specification of purposesWe may collect the following information:When you visit our site, we may automatically collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, IP address or ISP domain name as well as about your visits to and use of this website (length of visit and number of page views).Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters. This information is only used for the purpose of sending you newsletters and you can opt out at any time.We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:Internal record keeping.We may use the information to improve our website.2. CookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to visitors’ needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.We use Google Analytics to generate statistical information on the use of this website. The data are collected and stored by Google and presented to us in the form of report tables and charts. The data do not include any personal information.Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.3. Security of your personal dataWe are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.4. Links to other websitesOur website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.5. Policy amendmentsWe may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally in order to familiarise yourself with possible changes and to ensure you are happy with them. We will also actively inform you about major policy amendments as they arise.6. Your rightsYou have the right of access, free of charge, to the information about you that we hold, and to have erroneous information corrected. Requests for copies of the information we hold about you must be made in writing, signed, dated and accompanied by a copy of an identification document. Requests will be process by SCI within 30 days.You may withdraw any consent you have previously provided to us, or object at any time on legitimate grounds, to the processing of your personal information. We will comply with your request as soon as possible and within 30 days.If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us.7. How to contact usIf you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, or if you would like us to update information we hold about you or your preferences, please write to us by email or by post.8. Your consent to this policyBy using this site, you implicitly agree to accept SCI’s privacy policy. If you register you explicitly consent to the collection and processing of your personal data according to the terms and principles described in this policy.The use of this website is governed by Belgian law. This privacy policy is based on the Law of December 8, 1992 on Privacy Protection in relation to the Processing of Personal Data as modified by the law of December 11, 1998 implementing Directive 95/46/EC as well as the General Data Protection Policy of 2018.All disputes relating to or originating from the use of this website shall be exclusively submitted to the courts of Belgium, which will have exclusive jurisdiction in relation to such disputes. This Policy was last updated on 25 May 2018.For more information, please consult our Data Protection Policy and our Data Audit and Compliance Plan.Service Civil InternationalBelgiëlei 372018 AntwerpenBelgiumBE.0451.967.243
Our websites 2020: 100 years of SCI Workcamps Long-term volunteering SCI archivesJoin the movement! Find your local organisation Volunteer! Learn Participate Become a partner organisation FAQ Newsletter Contact us© 2020 The Association of Service Civil International Privacy and cookie policyService Civil InternationalBelgiëlei 372018 AntwerpenBelgiumBE.0451.967.243
Our websites 2020: 100 years of SCI Workcamps Long-term volunteering SCI archivesJoin the movement! Find your local organisation Volunteer! Learn Participate Become a partner organisation FAQ Newsletter Contact us Privacy and cookie policy© 2020 The Association of Service Civil InternationalService Civil InternationalBelgiëlei 372018 AntwerpenBelgiumBE.0451.967.243
Our websites 2020: 100 years of SCI Workcamps Long-term volunteering SCI archives FAQ Newsletter Contact us Privacy and cookie policy© 2020 The Association of Service Civil International
